govmint.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy-Policy

Welcome to GovMint.com® (this “Site”).

In this policy, we may use "we," "our," "us" and "GovMint.com" to refer to GovMint.com®, which includes its affiliated companies, New York Mint®, Asset Marketing Services®, and First Federal Coin Corp®.

At GovMint.com, we respect your privacy and take great care to safeguard your personal information in our possession. Your preferences for use of your information are our priority.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ACCEPT THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED BELOW.

This Privacy Policy covers all of the personal information we collect through this Site. This Privacy Policy does not necessarily apply to any offline collection of your personal information. Note that we are not responsible for content or privacy policies on any web site not operated by GovMint.com to which the Site links or that links to the Site.

To learn more about our Privacy Policy, click on the links below: 

GovMint.com Privacy Policy Overview

  * Categories of Information We Collect
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Share Your Information
  * Social Media Interactions
  * Links to Other Websites and Services
  * Manage Your Account Preferences
  * Children's Privacy
  * Security
  * Policy Changes
  * Additional Information
  * California Residents

Our Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference and is part of GovMint.com’s **[Terms of Use](http://www.govmint.com/terms-conditions)** (“Terms of Use”) governing your use of this Site. Our Terms of Use contain the terms on which you may purchase products through this Site. Please take a few minutes to review our Terms of Use, if you have not already done so. You may access the current version of the Terms of Use at any time by clicking on the link marked “Terms and Conditons” at the bottom of any page of this Site.

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on this Site, and indicate the effective date of the Policy at the bottom of each page. Your use of this Site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through this Site after the effective date will be subject to the revised Policy terms.

If you have any other questions or concerns regarding how GovMint.com manages, accesses or uses your personal information, please write us at 14101 Southcross Drive, Burnsville, Minnesota 55337, e-mail us at [Privacy@GovMint.com](mailto:privacy@govmint.com) or call 1-800-721-0320 Mon-Fri 8am to 6pm CT.

**GovMint.com Privacy Policy Overview**

Welcome to GovMint.com. As a customer of GovMint.com, we respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. We want you to understand what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of this information.

In this policy, "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), address (city, state, zip code), e-mail address, telephone number, etc.

This Privacy Policy governs your experience on this website and in our catalogs unless otherwise indicated.

**Categories of Information We Collect**

We collect personal information that you provide to us when you use this Site, and when you communicate or interact with us. For example, the information you provide when you register online or update your account, log-in, place an order or make a return with us (online, via phone, mail, email, fax or catalog), communicate online with our customer service representatives, opt-in to receive emails, opt-in to receive mobile messages or social media notifications from us, shop online, request a catalog or other content and communications from us, participate in a sweepstakes, contest, promotion or survey, join our social networking sites, interact with our mobile sites or mobile applications, work with our sales representatives to purchase items not available on our websites, use one of our social media services (i.e., GovMint.com’s Facebook page or YouTube channel), or when you contact us with a comment, question or complaint.

In order to serve you better, we may combine information you give to us on this Site with information you give to us through our catalog, mailings, mobile messaging, or telephone communications. We may also supplement the information we collect through this Site with information that is publicly available (such as information based on your zip code) and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Marketing Partners.

When you visit our websites we may also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or other device identifiers, browser information, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, location, date/time stamp and clickstream data. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. Note that the information we collect in this manner does not identify you personally, however, if you have created an account with us or have made a purchase through our Site, we may link the information provided by your browser to information that identifies you personally and use it for the purposes set forth in How We Use Your Information.

Our website uses "cookie" and "web beacon" technology. We use cookies and web beacons to identify your device, provide website user authentication, conduct fraud prevention and management services, distinguish you from other visitors, record your IP address and understand your use of our site, and identify the name of the Web site from which you linked to GovMint.com. This information is used for fulfilling contracts with our business partners, and to help us serve you better by improving our website design, as well as our products, services, and promotions. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. Information obtained through cookies and web beacons may be shared with or obtained by service providers on our behalf. More information is available under How We Share Your Information.

A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available. A web beacon is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image and is used in conjunction with a cookie.

When you visit our website, we may use both a session and a persistent cookie. This GovMint.com-placed cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID) that is used to track your usage of our website and in some cases, your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is only saved in this GovMint.com-placed cookie if you register with us. A web beacon allows us to capture certain additional types of information about a visitor's actions on a web site, such as a visitor's cookie number, the time, date, duration and number of page views, a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed, and details about any items that were purchased.

If you register with us, this GovMint.com-placed cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our website and provides you with access to your account information. If you save your information with or order from us, we may also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our website. If you have not saved your information with or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use the personal information that we collect to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products, services and experience. For example, we may collect and use your information:

  * To provide you with the products, information or services you request;
  * For security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
  * To provide you with the best possible customer service experience;
  * To provide you with a personalized experience when you use this Site;
  * To display personalized advertising when you visit this Site;
  * To contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you, with your permission;
  * To contact you with information and notices related to your use of this Site;
  * To invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
  * To improve the content, usability and functionality of this Site;
  * To improve our products and services;
  * To improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
  * To assist in law enforcement and respond to subpoenas;
  * To perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy or in any other agreement between you and GovMint.com.

**How We Share Your Information**

We share the information we collect from and about you within GovMint.com, which includes all subsidiaries and affiliates. We also share the information with a limited number of third parties, as described in this policy. When GovMInt.com allows these third parties access to your information, we require them to take commercially reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of your information and we do not permit them to use it in any way other than for the limited purpose for which it is provided.

_Service Providers_. GovMint.com shares personal information with companies and organizations that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies that provide support services to us (such as credit card processing services, data storage services, and web hosting services), or that help us market our products and services (such as third-party marketing and data hygiene companies).

_Marketing Partners_. From time to time, we may share your information, including without limitation your mailing and/or email address (but not your credit card information), with unaffiliated third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you and who have their own privacy policy in place. If you do not wish to receive marketing materials from these third parties, or to learn more about managing the ways in which we use or share your information, click on Manage Your Account Preferences.

_Business Transfers_. In the event that the company’s business assets are sold or transferred, or as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer the corresponding information regarding our customers. In such an event, the acquiring or surviving company’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

_Legal Requirements_. We may disclose personal information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply applicable terms or conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our company, our customers, or others.

**Social Media Interactions**

GovMint.com invites you to socialize and share your purchases with your friends using Social Media tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+, YouTube, etc. If you choose to use these tools, you may be sharing certain profile elements, including your comments. This sharing is subject to each social media program's privacy policies. We offer links on our site to “Share” or “Like” our site or products for many of the popular social sites. To remove a “Share” or “Like” or to delete your comments you will have to make those changes directly on that specific social site.

**Links to Other Websites and Services**

GovMint.com’s Site may include links to other Internet sites, content, or videos (embedded or direct links) maintained by third parties ('Linked Sites'). GovMint.com provides Linked Sites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of Linked Sites does not imply endorsement by GovMint.com of the Linked Sites. You access Linked Sites at your own risk and by accessing them you may leave GovMint.com's website. Linked Sites are not under the control of GovMint.com and GovMint.com is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including the privacy policies or tracking technologies they may use. We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy to determine how they will handle any personally identifying information they collect from you.

**Manage Your Account Preferences**

To update us with your preferences, or to opt-out of receiving communications from us, you may contact us using one of the following methods:

  * Call 1-800-721-0320 Mon-Fri 8am to 6pm CT, or
  * E-mail [Privacy@GovMint.com](mailto:privacy@govmint.com), or
  * Send your request to GovMint.com, Attn: Privacy, 14101 Southcross Drive, Burnsville MN 55337

Please note your preference as stated below:

"I prefer not to receive e-mail advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events from you." (You may also click the designated link at the bottom of all GovMint.com e-mail advertisements to be removed from future e-mail updates.)

"I prefer not to receive direct mail advertisements, such as periodic catalogs and mailings regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events from you." (Please note that direct mail requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective.)

"I prefer not to receive marketing phone calls such as special events, promotions or new products from a GovMint.com sales representative or the company."

“I prefer not to receive marketing materials from other affiliated third-party companies.”

In providing us with your preferences, please be sure to include all of your emails, telephone numbers, addresses or other personal information you may have used to communicate with us, so that GovMint.com may better accommodate your request.

**Children's Privacy**

GovMint.com will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years old please do not provide your information on our website. If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to GovMint.com for any purpose, we will delete it.

**Security**

We appreciate the trust you place in GovMint.com when sharing personal information and thus are committed to recording and storing this information in a secure way. We maintain reasonable, physical, technical and procedural measures to limit access to your personal information. Only authorized individuals of our company are able to see your information and use it for appropriate purposes.

**Policy Changes**

This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on our website.

**Additional Information**

If you would prefer to make your purchase via telephone, just give us a call at 1-800-642-9160. Our Sales Representatives will be happy to assist you.

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at:

GovMint.com Privacy  
14101 Southcross Drive  
Burnsville, MN 55337  
1-800-721-0320 Mon-Fri 8am-6pm CT  

**CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

**California Privacy Rights**

California law entitles residents to ask GovMint.com for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or with corporate affiliates. If you want to request a notice or have any questions about GovMint.com privacy practices, please contact us at [Privacy@GovMint.com](mailto:privacy@govmint.com).

**California Civil Code Section 1789.3**

If you have a question or complaint regarding the Site, please send an email to [CustomerService@GovMint.com](mailto:customerservice@govmint.com). You may also contact us in writing at GovMint.com, Attn: Customer Service, 14101 Southcross Drive, Burnsville, Minnesota 55337. California residents may reach the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs by mail at 1625 North Market Blvd., Sacramento, CA 95834 or by telephone at (800) 952-5210.

This Privacy Policy was revised on November 12, 2013.
